All right, Peter.
You made it to the bonus round.
- Congratulations.
- Thanks, Regis.
Okay, the category
is "Actor and Show. "
So, we need five consonants and a vowel.
Oh, okay. Um...
"Z." Four.
"Q."
Another "Q."
Uh...
A third "Q."
And the Batman symbol.
Okay, no help there. Fifteen seconds.
If you want to take a shot at it, talk it out.
Is it Alex Karras in Webster?
I don't believe it.
Oh, my God! I just took a shot in the dark!
Holy crap!
Okay. You have $1,300.
Why don't you go ahead and pick out
some prizes from our showcase?
Okay, let's see. Oh, boy!
Everything looks nice. Um...
All right, I'll take
the ceramic Dalmatian for $600.
And, uh, boy, that TV looks nice.
Uh, give me the one free week
of maid service.
And, uh, I'll take the hat rack.
Um, hey, how much
for that fat guy in the circle?
I don't see a price tag on that.
That's you.
- Oh, embarrassing.
Okay, well, in that case,
I'll take the rest on a gift certificate.
Oh, sweetie, you look so handsome on TV.
I can't believe you actually won.
But I suppose it's not the strangest thing
I've seen on a game show.
Like when Adam West was on Jeopardy.
All right, players.
The answer once again is,
"It was the first spacecraft
to land on the surface of Mars. "
Adam, what was your response?
"Kebert Xela. "
Only saying his name backwards
can send him back
to the fifth dimension, where he belongs.
All right, whip them out, woman.
It's time for the afternoon meal.
My goodness, Stewie.
I guess you're hungry.
Honey, not so rough this time.
Mommy's very sore.
And, by the way, let's be clear.
I only like you as a friend.
Hi. I'm Joan. I'm your maid for the week.
Me Peter. You maid.
Um, I do speak English.
You maid, clean for me, Peter.
You clean Peter mess.
Peter, stop it. Welcome to our home, Joan.
I'm Lois. Won't you come in?
Oh, boy! My own maid.
This is gonna kick more ass
than that magical ride I took.
Well, we are officially lost.
Shut up, Ricky! Just shut up right now!
Unless the next words
out of your mouth are directions
how to get back to the fish skeleton,
I'm gonna punch you right in the stomach!
Joan, it's great to have you here.
No one's cleaned
my belly button in a long time.
Lois is afraid to go near there
and my fingers are too thick.
What is this?
A carton of Parliaments?
I haven't smoked in 10 years.
Hey, keep digging.
Oh, ColecoVision.
Yeah! This could be a fun afternoon.
Mr. Griffin, this is
unbelievably humiliating.
Hey, hey, Lois wants me
to go to the store and the car's low on gas.
Oh, crap!
This is truly a sight to behold.
An awesome spectacle.
Peter Griffin, a once great champion
of the motor speedway
now a study in moppishness.
The hell I am!
Hiya!
We now return
to Malcolm in the Middle.
And I told you boys
to pick up your clothes!
And who left the wet towel on the bed?
I swear to God,
sometimes I feel like just going on strike!
What would you all do if I went on strike?
Huh? What would you do?
I'm talking to you! You know what?
That's what I'm gonna do!
I'm gonna go on strike!
And you can all try living without me!
You ever think about that, huh?
That's what I'm gonna do.
I'm gonna do that.
Kids, we're free.
We're finally free.
Ouch. Damn, that hurts.
What happened?
I was breastfeeding Stewie,
and he bit me again.
I think he might have
even broken the skin.
I see. Um...
Maybe I should, uh,
you know, uh, look at it.
I, uh... I, uh...
I have seen a lot of medical shows.
You see, the areola is very tender here.
And I think one of his new teeth may have
bitten down right on a duct.
I'm sorry. What?
I don't know what to do, Brian.
Breastfeeding's just so painful
since Stewie's teeth are coming in.
Now I know how Alec Baldwin feels
when he feeds his brothers.
There you go. There you go.
Eat up, Stephen. You're the weakest.
Well, maybe it's time to wean Stewie.
I suppose it would make my life easier.
You know what? I'll give it a try.
- Thanks, Brian.
- No problem.
Any other problems you have, too,
like, for example, around your underpants
that you want me to take a look at,
I could take a look at that, too.
Huh?
Please pull down your underpants.
All right, boys. It's my maid's last night.
So we got to make the most of it.
I filled this watermelon with
chocolate pudding and M-80 firecrackers.
Hey, Meg. Will you hold this for Daddy?
Okay. Why?
Uh, it's a present.
It's a thanks-for-being-
such-a-sweetie watermelon.
So you'll hang onto that?
Yeah, sure.
This is weird. Am I supposed to eat this?
I hate you! I hate you!
Oh, maid.
Oh, my God!
Everybody, this is Joan.
- Hi.
- Hello.
Hey, there.
I mean, it's nice to
pleasure your acquaintance.
I mean, would you like
to go out to dinner tomorrow night?
I'd love to.
God, he works fast.
Hey, Quagmire,
is that a banana in your pocket
or a erection in your pocket?
Do you want to say 9:00?
Sure. See you then.
Oh, my God! I'm in love.
Time for dinner, sweetie.
Very well, then. Take off your shirt.
No, honey. No, no.
Tonight we're gonna have formula instead.
That's more disgusting
than when Peter went through
that Daisy Dukes phase.
So who's up
for some hoops at the park, huh?
Oh, there you are.
Come here, you basketball.
It's like a walrus flossing.
I know it's different than you're used to.
But you'll see it's just as good.
Yes. That's what we were promised
about Jim Belushi
some 25 laugh-free years ago.
Wow, it's so lovely here, Glenn.
Well, this is our
three-week anniversary, Joan.
I wanted this date to be special.
You know,
this place is unique because if you're lucky,
some nights around sunset,
the screaming black dolphins come out.
Oh, wow! Really?
I've heard they're just beautiful.
What's going on, man?
Oh, what's going on yourself?
- I almost drowned yesterday.
- Oh, man!
It's wet out here.
Oh, look at them.
They're magical, aren't they?
Listen, Joan. I have
something very important to ask you.
Hey, James.
Mmm-hmm.
I'm gonna see how long
I can hold my breath.
I see you breathing out your hole.
What is it, Glenn?
Joan, I've decided
I want to spend my life with you.
Will you marry me?
Of course I will.
Nothing would make me
happier than to be Mrs. Quagmire.
Hey, man.
I see you got some seaweed on your tail.
Where? What? Oh!
You know I'm just playing with you.
Man, you are...
Oh, I thought
you was talking about other seaweed.
You know I got jokes.
I'm gonna slap you with my fin.
Man, I never would have thought
Quagmire would get married.
No, no. I know Quagmire.
And I'm telling you,
this has got to be some kind of prank.
You know, like that prank
I pulled on Ashton Kutcher.
Ashton, come here.
You've just been tomahawked.
That's my show. Tomahawked.
So, how's the weaning going?
Oh, it's horrible.
Giving up breast milk
is the hardest thing I've ever had to do.
I'll bet the founding fathers had
an easier time writing the Bill of Rights.
All right, we're done.
You think the language
in the Second Amendment is clear enough?
- You know, about the right to bear arms?
- Of course it's clear.
Every American has the right
to hang a pair of bear arms on their wall.
How could that possibly be misconstrued?
All right. Fantastic then.
Wait. You know what?
Before we send this to the printer,
let's take that abortion thing out.
Boy, I never thought we'd be going
to Quagmire's for an engagement party.
I'm telling you guys, he's putting us on.
He's the same old Quagmire.
Hey there, neighbors. Are you lost?
I'm just joshing. Of course
we're expecting you. Come on in, friends.
Uh-uh, if you all will just
take your shoes off there.
Joan and I kind of do the Japanese thing.
Uh-oh, foot odor.
I have to go.
I have, uh, terrible foot odor.
Glenn, your place looks wonderful.
I feel like I can touch things in here now.
We brought you guys a bottle of wine.
Oh, Montrachet!
I like our friends.
So, Joan and I just love
Without a Trace, don't we, honey?
- Yeah, it's all right.
- We think it's all right.
What are you talking about? You hate CBS.
Ooh. "Hate" is a word
we don't use in this house.
Joan and I always say, " If you don't have
anything nice to say about someone,
"don't say anything at all. "
We say that, right, honey?
- Sometimes.
- Sometimes we say that.
Hey, Quagmire.
Check out this month's Hustler, huh.
- Quagmire?
- Now, this is neat.
These people have put
an old-fashioned Colonial spinning wheel
in the center
of their living room, as furniture.
Oh, that's what I want in my house.
All right, Quagmire.
Time for your lap dance.
No, guys. I can't do that.
It's degrading to women.
Come on, Quagmire. It's got to be you.
I'm married, Cleveland's got foot odor,
and Joe's dead from the waist down.
Why do you bring me here?
Oh, Brian, my breasts are so sore.
And they've gotten
so engorged from the weaning,
I've gone up two bra sizes.
What did you do with the old bras?
Okay. Got to time this just right.
One, two, three!
Help! Somebody get this baby off me!
Stewie! I'm so sorry.
By the way, you call those
cheap implants boobs?
Those aren't boobs. They are lies!
I can't believe it.
Quagmire's gone all
sissy-man Alan Alda on us!
Well, what can we do about it?
The wedding's tomorrow.
There's only one thing to do.
We got to break it up.
Gosh, Peter,
thanks so much for being my best man.
Oh, it's my pleasure.
In fact, I got a wedding surprise for you.
All right, back it up, guys.
I know you got a foot fetish
so I got you this Statue of Liberty's foot.
Oh, thanks, Peter.
But Joan is all the foot I need now.
What? But, Quagmire,
that's the real foot from the Statue...
No, no. I'm okay.
Hey, do you have any idea
what I went through to get this?
A lot. A real lot.
You think this is just,
"Oh, here comes Peter
"with the Statue of Liberty's
foot. Oh, isn't that a gas?"
No. No. The reality, the real reality
of getting this together was staggering.
You know, this cost me $437,000.
Don't ask me how I got it.
I had to call in a whole bunch
of favors from people I've never even met.
So the very least you can do
is just rub up against... I don't know.
Well, if you want I can...
No, no. No, no, it's fine. No. Whatever.
Whatever. Just go to your wedding, man.
No. No. No. No. Take...
Just get it out of here.
Peter, what's the matter?
This is a happy occasion.
No, it's not, Lois. It's horrible.
You don't know what happens to a man
when he gets married.
It's like a disease
that rots you from the inside out.
I know, Peter, but... Oh, damn it.
I can't believe
how much my breasts have swollen.
Oh, look out. Champagne.
Peter, stop.
Oh, Lois, you're all wet.
Here, let me jiggle you dry.
Giggity giggity God!
I've made a terrible mistake!
Oh, my God, you blew it up.
You really did it.
Damn you all to hell!
Oh, God. I got to get out of this marriage.
Cleveland, how did you get out of yours?
You slept with my wife.
It's easy, Quagmire.
Just tell her to hit the bricks.
Yeah. You've gotten
out of commitments before.
Wow, that was great.
Sure was. See you.
But you said we were gonna get married.
No. I only said that
so you'd googooity my geshmoigen.
So, anyway, what I'm trying to tell you is,
some of the guys thought
we should get a divorce.
What?
But I told them they
didn't know what they were talking about.
Good. Good. 'Cause if you ever left me,
I'd have to cut myself.
And then I'd cut you.
I love you, Glenn.
I love you, too, insane-woman-I'm-having-
second-thoughts-about.
- What?
- All right.
Yes. Sleep away, woman.
But I'm here to claim
what's rightfully mine.
Yeah, yeah. Oh, yeah.
Oh, that's the stuff. Yeah, yeah.
Dear God! I've got to get a hold of myself.
Look at me
sucking pilfered milk off a dirty carpet.
I'm as pathetic
as the fat man when he tries to read.
- Hey, Lois, what's this word?
- "Evel. "
- And this one?
- "Kneivel. "
- "Was. "
- And this one?
- "Born. "
- "In. "
- And this one?
- "Montana. "
Hey, Lois. Did you know
that Evel Kneivel was born in Montana?
You didn't tell her?
Look, I told you she was gonna kill herself.
What was I supposed to do?
Let her. No, that's not funny.
Wait a second.
We know she's gonna be upset
if you dump her.
But if something happened that
was out of your control...
- What do you mean?
- I mean we're gonna fake your death.
This is the best idea
I've had since I invented that soda.
Gentlemen, I give you Crystal Pepsi.
All the great taste of regular Pepsi
but without the troublesome opacity.
Well, what if you're drinking
a regular Pepsi
and somebody is coming at you
with a knife, huh?
You won't be able to see him
past your Pepsi.
And then, who's dead, huh? You.
You! You're dead! Stabbed!
Crystal Pepsi.
All right, fellas. I think we did it.
This may be
the most absolutely perfect fake death
in the history of fake deaths.
What do you guys want?
Joan, um, you mind if we come in?
There's, um... There's been an accident.
This is, uh, not gonna be easy,
but it's something you should see.
So, anyway, here's Quagmire
walking through the park,
minding his own business.
I just happened to be there
with my video camera
when a ninja shows up!
And then a Nazi came!
And then an evil pots-and-pans robot!
Destroy.
I imagine you're probably wondering
what happened to the body.
Well, we thought of that.
Oh, no! Quagmire's dead!
Wait! We might still be able to save...
Oh, no!
We are so, so sorry for your loss.
Is this a joke?
I wish it were, Joan. I wish it were a joke.
But these things happen, you know?
You go for a walk in the park one day,
and wheelchair ninjas, and Nazis, and
pots-and-pans robots show up to kill you,
and dinosaurs show up to eat the remains.
You've seen the news.
You're not fooling anyone.
All right, fellows. Plan B.
Plan B, Quagmire.
Hi, honey. I'm home.
Heart attack!
Glenn, sweetheart! Is he all right?
No, he's dead. I can tell. I'm a cop.
Oh, my God! Are you sure?
You know what'll prove it?
When people die, they void their bowels.
I said, when people die,
they void their bowels.
Oh, my God!
What a jackass.
- Well, you look a lot better.
- I did it, Brian!
Through sheer force of will,
I kicked my addiction to breast milk.
I just had to find a way
to make breasts seem repulsive.
- Yeah. How did you do that?
- I watched In The Cut.
Meg Ryan topless. No, thanks. No, thanks.
Stewie, Mommy has a surprise for you.
What are you doing?
Oh, Brian, I thought
I was ready to wean him.
But I just miss the bonding.
No, no! No, put me down! I beg of you!
I just kicked the stuff. Damn you!
You sick, twisted...
I hate you.
I love it.
I will kill you.
You sure Quagmire's okay in there?
No problem.
He's got half an hour of oxygen.
We'll sneak back later and dig him up.
Sorry, I'm late.
I had a meeting over at NBC about Joey.
Death? What are you doing here?
Nobody's dying today.
Not according to my paperwork.
Says here your buddy Quagmire
died of a heart attack.
I got to tell you,
I always thought it would be rectal trauma.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
What the hell are you doing?
Well, Mayor West is afraid of zombies.
So the city says
all caskets must be encased in concrete.
You'll thank me
when no one eats our brains.
You'll thank me.
Hold it! Stop the funeral.
Quagmire's not really dead.
Zombie!
Glenn, I thought I'd lost you.
Sorry, Mr. Quagmire, but I still need a body
to take back with me.
- So...
- No, you can't take him.
You know, this is probably not cool.
Just throwing it out there.
- She was suicidal.
- She was?
- Yeah, absolutely.
- I had heard that, too.
And her last name was Quagmire.
Well, good enough for me.
I got to go. I got tickets to Celine Dion.
I'm not gonna kill her,
I'm just gonna watch her die on her own.
Anyone? Anyone?
Ah, it's good to have you back, Quagmire.
It's good to be back, Peter.
Hey, Death, can you leave
that body here for another five minutes?
That's Quagmire.
Thank you for watching «Family Guy» on
www.FOX-fan.ru